{
    "subject": "resource/Eric_Feldt",
    "predicate": "property/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/New_Farm,_Queensland",
    "human_readable": "Eric Feldt died in New Farm, Queensland.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7910907864570618,
            "question": "Where did Eric Feldt die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7847318649291992,
            "question": "Was Eric Feldt born in Queensland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7084256410598755,
            "question": "What year did Eric Feldt die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2650895118713379,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Eric Feldt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2552454173564911,
            "question": "In what country is New Farm located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23211416602134705,
            "question": "What is New Farm known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19906680285930634,
            "question": "Is there any notable history associated with New Farm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18179544806480408,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from New Farm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12402617931365967,
            "question": "What are some popular attractions in New Farm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11455581337213516,
            "question": "What is the climate like in New Farm?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eric Feldt died in New Farm, Queensland.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4060_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular attractions in New Farm?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4060_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous people from New Farm?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4060_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any notable history associated with New Farm?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4060_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4060_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4060_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4060_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4060_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4060_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4060_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4060_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4060_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4060_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4060_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the context information states that Eric Feldt died in 1968 and there is no specific location mentioned. However, it does mention that he retired from the New Guinea administration and lived in Brisbane on a pension, but it does not specify where he died. Therefore, we cannot confirm whether he died in New Farm, Queensland."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not mention the place of death for Eric Augustus Feldt. While they provide information about his life and career, including his residence during parts of World War II in Townsville and Brisbane, there is no specific statement regarding where he died. Therefore, the given triple cannot be confirmed based on the context provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context that indicates Eric Feldt died in New Farm, Queensland.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context states Eric Feldt retired from the New Guinea administration and lived in Brisbane on a pension. It also mentions his death in 1968 without specifying a location other than Brisbane.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information mentions that Eric Feldt retired to Brisbane on a pension and lived there, which implies that he did not die in New Farm, Queensland.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention the place of Eric Feldt's death. It only provides his date of birth (1899) and date of death (1968), along with details about his life, career, and achievements. There is no specific information indicating that he died in New Farm, Queensland.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}